

yashbobde01@gmail.com | +91 7770099965

PROFILE

Sales Development Representative with work experience in B2B SAAS sales and business development in hospitality and pharmaceutical domain. I possess a strong understanding of both B2C and B2B sales, and my overall experience spans four years.

EXPERIENCE

Sales Development Representative, DevDynamics, Pune, India — April 2023 – August 2023 (5months: Full time)

- Developed and executed lead generation strategies.
- Utilized cold email campaigns and LinkedIn outreach to expand the prospect database and foster new business opportunities.
- Leveraged CRM software, such as HubSpot, to manage leads, track interactions, and ensure efficient follow-up processes.
- Successfully maintained a weekly cohort report in Excel, providing critical insights into sales performance and identifying areas for improvement.
- Conducted persuasive presentations to prospects, effectively communicating the value proposition and converting leads into clients.
- Demonstrated strong negotiation skills, leading to the closure of several key deals and exceeding quarterly sales targets.
- Achieved a 20 lakhs revenue for the organization in a span of 5 months.

IT Sales Executive, Qodequay Technologies, Pune, India — Jan 2023 – April 2023 (4months: Full time)

- US cold calling.
- Generating leads through the help of Sales Navigator.
- Building connection and rapport with CXOs over the LinkedIn by sending connection request on daily basis with message.
- Worked on CRM tools like HubSpot, Salesforce, Freshsales, Zoho etc.
- Worked on various Extensions like Apollo.io, MR-E and Build-with for getting personal details of the prospect.
- Sending mails to all leads which got generated on the same day itself.

Senior Relationship Manager, Club Mahindra Holidays Ltd, Pune, India — Feb 2021 – May 2022 (15months: Full time)

- Calling / Meeting and establishing connection with Club Mahindra's potential customer.
- Understanding their requirements and debriefing them about a suitable product plan.
- Working with the team leads and senior managers to complete monthly targets.

- Establishing contacts with newer leads and negotiating to convert them into customers.
- Maintaining a good relationship with existing customers and getting regular feedbacks.
- Aiding new customers to complete the onboarding procedure and with further bookings.
- Developing marketing strategy for attracting newer customers.
- Interpersonal and communication skills.
- Cold calling and lead generation.
- Negotiation skills and closing skills.

Sales Associate, Shri Narendra Medical and General Store (Pharmaceutical Wholesale distributor), Nanded, India — Oct 2018 - Oct 2020 (2 years: Full time)

- Working with team and senior managers to develop and implement new strategies for improving overall sales.
- Identifying and evaluating new business opportunities.
- Meeting and communicating with clients and pitching business prospects.
- Proposing ides for benefiting current client base.
- Meeting monthly sales targets.

EDUCATION

Savitribai Phule Pune University, Pune, India — MBA Marketing, 2020 - 2022

Savitribai Phule Pune University, Pune, India — BVoc Mass Communication, 2020

Higher secondary certificate, Basmat, India — 2015

Secondary school certificate, Basmat, India — 2013

CGPA: 8.93

CGPA: 8.93

CGPA: 8.93

CGPA: 6.9%

Percentage: 60%

Percentage: 61%